<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Akshat Patni</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Akshat Patni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploratory Data Analysis: Game of Thrones Characters</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this study, I’ve applied some basic data manipulation and statistical methods to one of my favorite works of fiction, the Game of Thrones series by George R.R. Martin! In particular, I wanted to differentiate between the influence of characters between the books compared to the show, seeing as how the two stories have greatly diverged. I also wanted to see which characters were the most influential overall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modeling, Testing, and Predicting: Diabetes Indicators amongst Pima Indian Females</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this study, I found a dataset that contains several variables with medical statistics for a population of Pima Indian females. These numeric variables outline various health factors that can help indicate the likelihood of an individual having diabetes. These factors include their number of pregnancies, blood glucose levels, diastolic blood pressure, skin thickness (indicative of body fat), BMI, 2 hour serum insulin, BMI, age, and Diabetes Pedigree Function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>  Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
